<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ms_project_android</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="no_record">Please record</string>
    <string name="record_in_progress">Recording</string>
    <string name="record_available">Record</string>


    <string name="info_title">Welcome to Emotion Classification Evaluation</string>
    <string name="info_info">
        In this app we want to evaluate the performance of our speech emotion recognition model.
        I this app we will ask you to record voice messages in 5 different emotional states:
        neutral, happy, sad, angry, fearful.
        To bring you into an emotional state. We will describe a situation for each emotion and
        ask you to record a response to the given situation.
        But this are just examples. If you have an better idea you can also record an different text.
        Important is that you try to do it in the given emotional state.
        The duration of you record should be around 1 minute or longer.
    </string>
    <string name="info_privacy">
        In the end we will ask you to share the results with us. So that we can evaluate them.
        Your records are analyzed on the device (NOT in the cloud)
        and will NOT be part of the send and analyzed data.
        Only the requested emotional state and the classification results are part of it.
        If you continue with the next steps you allow us to automatically analyze you records.
    </string>

    <string name="recognition_headline">Emotion Classification</string>
    <string name="recognition_task_name">Test Run</string>
    <string name="recognition_task">
        This is the Test Run. It will make you familiar with the app.
        Tab on the action button on the bottom left to start the voice recording
        and tab it again to stop it.
    </string>

    <string name="recognition_emo0_headline">Emotion Classification</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo0_task_name">Neutral Emotion</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo0_task">
        Describe your surroundings and the weather in a neutral way
    </string>

    <string name="recognition_emo1_headline">Emotion Classification</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo1_task_name">Happy Emotion</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo1_task">
        Record a happy emotion
    </string>neutral

    <string name="recognition_emo2_headline">Emotion Classification</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo2_task_name">Sad Emotion</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo2_task">
        Record a sad emotion
    </string>

    <string name="recognition_emo3_headline">Emotion Classification</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo3_task_name">Angry Emotion</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo3_task">
        Your flatmate Jerry, did again "forgott" to clean the dishes. Even though you told him yesterday.\n
        It is going like this since weeks now.\n
        Record a angry voice message and tell jerry that you can not live like this anymore and he should clean the dishes immediately when he comes home.
        Otherwise you might change the password of your netflix account which he also uses.
    </string>

    <string name="recognition_emo4_headline">Emotion Classification</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo4_task_name">Fearful Emotion</string>
    <string name="recognition_emo4_task">
        Record a fearful emotion
    </string>

    <string name="share_headline">Share your Results</string>
    <string name="share_info">
        Thank you for helping us to evaluate our project work.\n
        Please share you results now with us.\n
        As mentioned in the beginning only the statistics will be shared and not you records.
    </string>

</resources>